
This Android app was built for the Final Year Project of my B.Eng in Dublin City University, Ireland. It was an exploration into the capabilities for ML-based image classification to innovate within the calorie-counting/diet-management applicaton industry. Namely, the application uses a retrained version of the MobileNets image classification model to perform this on Android - implemented with the lightweight TensorFlow Lite ML library. This was on the leading edge of mobile-based ML in 2017/18!

Please excuse the code quality: my project was based on the apps' functionality and on my research, so code quality lapsed in the rush to complete the project. It will be cleaned up eventually!

Copyright © 2019 LukeScales